Guide to the Witold Gombrowicz Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Clippings, 1933-1998; Series XI; 74.94; (48 boxes)
  - WHOLE ISSUES CONTAINING ARTICLES PERTAINING TO GOMBROWICZ
    - French
      - Le Monde Nr, 15822, 1995 Dec 9 (Box 63, Folder 1634)
      - Le Monde, 1994 Jun 30
      - Nouvel Observateur, Nr 611, 1976 Jul-Aug (Box 63, Folder 1635)
      - Nouvel Observateur, Nr 1616, 1995 Oct-Nov (Box 63, Folder 1636)
      - Les Nouvelles, 1984 Apr 12-18 (Box 63, Folder 1637)
      - Nouvelles littéraires, Nr 2533, 1973 May 20
      - Ombres blanches, 1996 Mar-Apr (Box 63, Folder 1638)
      - Pariscope Nr 1116, 1989 Oct 11-17 (Box 63, Folder 1639)
      - Pariscope Nr 1331, 1993 Nov 24-30 (Box 63, Folder 1640)
      - Politis Nr 36, 1988 Nov 4-10 (Box 63, Folder 1641)
      - Public. Le journal du Théâtre national de la Colline, Nr 6, 1989-90
      - Public. Le journal du Théâtre national de la Colline, 1997 Jan-Jul
      - Quinzaine littéraire, Nr 27, 1967 May 1-15
      - Quinzaine littéraire, Nr 236, 1976
      - Quinzaine littéraire, Nr 257 (2 copies), 1977
      - Quinzaine littéraire, Nr 416, 1984
      - Quinzaine littéraire, Nr 697, 1996
      - Quinzaine littéraire, Nr 698, 1996
      - Revue des sciences humaines, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 1642)
      - Télérama Nr 2426, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 1643)
      - Théâtre Nr 449, 1970 May 15 (Box 63, Folder 1644)
      - Théâtre en Pologne. The Theatre in Poland, Nr 7 (fragment), 1980 (Box 63, Folder 1645)
      - Théâtre en Pologne. The Theatre in Poland, Nr 5, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 1646)
      - Théâtres, Nr 6, 1989 Nov
      - Valeurs actuelles Nr 3121, 1996 Jul 20-26 (Box 63, Folder 1647)
      - Vice versa, Nr 18-19, 1987 May-Jun
    - German
      - Carl Hanser Verlag
        - Catalogue Herbst 1983 (Box 63, Folder 1648)
        - Catalogue Früjahr 1984 (Box 63, Folder 1649)
        - Catalogue Herbst 1984 (Box 63, Folder 1650)
        - Catalogue Frühjahr 1985 (Box 64, Folder 1651)
        - Catalogue Frühjahr 1987 (Box 64, Folder 1652)
        - Catalogue Herbst 1988 (Box 64, Folder 1653)
        - Catalogue Herbst 1991 (Box 64, Folder 1654)
        - Catalogue Frühjahr 1996 (Box 64, Folder 1655)
        - Catalogue Herbst 1997 (Box 64, Folder 1656)
      - Fischer Taschenbücher [Catalogue], 1984 May-Oct (Box 64, Folder 1657)
      - Der Ferdydurkist, nr 1, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1658)
      - Der Ferdydurkist, nr 2, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1659)
      - Proszenium Nr 131, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 1660)
      - Theater heute Nr 4, 1971 Apr (Box 64, Folder 1661)
      - Theater heute Nr 12, 1980 Dec (Box 64, Folder 1662)
    - Hungarian
      - Könyvvilág, 1984 Aug (Box 64, Folder 1663)
    - Italian
      - Leggere Nr 44, 1992 Sep (Box 64, Folder 1664)
      - Teatro, Nr 63, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 1665)
    - Polish
      - Dialog, 1985 Jul 7 (Box 64, Folder 1666)
      - Gazeta Wyborcza. Magazyn, Nr 13, 1993 Jun 4
      - Gazeta Wyborcza. Magazyn, Nr 4 (100), 1995 Jan 27
      - Magazyn Wilenski, Nr 9, 1994 Sep (Box 64, Folder 1667)
      - Przekrój, Nr 47 (2474), 1992 Nov 22
      - Teatr, Nr 1 (880), 1990 Jan (Box 64, Folder 1668)
      - Teatr, Nr 7/8, 1991 Jul-Aug (Box 64, Folder 1669)
      - Teatr, Nr 12, 1991 Dec (Box 64, Folder 1670)
      - Teatr, Nr 2, 1992 Feb (Box 64, Folder 1671)
      - Warszawa
        See: Warszawa, box 62, folder 1600
    - Spanish
      - ABC literario, Nr 498, 1990 Aug 18 (Box 64, Folder 1672)
      - Diners, Nr 133, 1981 Apr (Box 64, Folder 1673)
      - Gente y la actualidad, Nr 268, 1970 Sep 10
      - Opinion cultural, 1972 Jun 18
      - Solcalmo, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 1674)
      - Teatro, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 1675)
      - Vanguardia española, 1991 May 28
    - Swedish
      - Teaterronden Nr 14, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 1676)
      - Teaterronden Nr 19, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 1677)
      - Teaterronden Nr 23, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 1678)
  - NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS
    - Bulgarian
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 1679)
      - Clippings, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 1680)
      - Clippings, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 1681)
    - Croatian
      - Clippings, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 1682)
      - Clippings, 1970, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1683)
    - Czech
      - Clippings, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 1684)
      - Clippings, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 1685)
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 1686)
      - Clippings, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 1687)
      - Clippings, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 1688)
    - Dutch
      - Clippings, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1689)
      - Clippings, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1690)
      - Clippings, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 1691)
      - Clippings, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 1692)
      - Clippings, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 1693)
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 1694-1695)
      - Clippings, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 1696)
      - Clippings, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 1697)
      - Clippings, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1698)
      - Clippings, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 1699)
      - Clippings, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 1700-1701)
      - Clippings, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 1702)
      - Clippings, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 1703)
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 1704)
      - Clippings, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 1705)
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 1706)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1707)
    - English
      - Clippings, 1958 (Box 69, Folder 1708)
      - Clippings, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 1709)
      - Clippings, 1962 (Box 69, Folder 1710)
      - Clippings, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1711)
      - Clippings, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 1712)
      - Clippings, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1713-1714)
      - Clippings, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 1715)
      - Clippings, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 1716)
      - Clippings, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 1717)
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 1718)
      - Clippings, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 1719)
      - Clippings, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 1720)
      - Clippings, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 1721)
      - Clippings, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 1722)
      - Clippings, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 1723)
      - Clippings, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 1724)
      - Clippings, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 1725)
      - Clippings, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 1726)
      - Clippings, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 1727)
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 1728)
      - Clippings, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 1729)
      - Clippings, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 1730)
      - Clippings, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 1731)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1732)
    - Finnish
      - Clippings, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 1733)
    - French
      - Clippings, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 1734)
      - Clippings, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 1735)
      - Clippings, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 1736)
      - Clippings, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 1737)
      - Clippings, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 1738-1739)
      - Clippings, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 1740-1742)
        Includes articles in Spanish
      - Clippings, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 1743-1744)
      - Clippings, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 1745)
        Includes WG's annotations
      - Clippings, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1746)
      - Clippings, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 1747)
      - Clippings, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 1748)
      - Clippings, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 1749)
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1750)
      - Clippings, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1751)
      - Clippings, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 1752-1755)
      - Clippings, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 1756-1757)
      - Clippings, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 1758-1761)
      - Clippings, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 1762-1766)
      - Clippings, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 1767)
      - Clippings, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 1768)
      - Clippings, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 1769)
      - Clippings, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 1770)
      - Clippings, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 1771)
      - Clippings, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 1772)
      - Clippings, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 1773)
        Includes an annotation by Constantin Jelenski
      - Clippings, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 1774)
      - Clippings, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 1775)
      - Clippings, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 1776)
      - Clippings, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 1777)
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 1778-1781)
      - Clippings, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 1782)
      - Clippings, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 1783)
      - Clippings, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 1784)
      - Clippings, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 1785)
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 1786)
      - Clippings, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 1787)
      - Clippings, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 1788)
      - Clippings, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 1789)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 1790-1792)
    - German
      - Clippings, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1793)
      - Clippings, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 1794)
      - Clippings, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 1795)
      - Clippings, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 1796)
      - Clippings, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 1797-1800)
      - Clippings, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 1801-1802)
      - Clippings, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 1803-1806)
      - Clippings, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 1807-1808)
      - Clippings, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1809-1810)
        Includes WG's annotations and French translations
      - Clippings, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1811-1812)
      - Clippings, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 1813-1814)
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 1815-1817)
      - Clippings, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 1818-1819)
      - Clippings, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 1820-1822)
      - Clippings, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 1823)
      - Clippings, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 1824)
      - Clippings, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 1825)
      - Clippings, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 1826)
      - Clippings, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1827)
      - Clippings, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 1828-1830)
        Includes French translations of articles
      - Clippings, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 1831)
      - Clippings, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 1832)
      - Clippings, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 1833)
      - Clippings, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 1834)
      - Clippings, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 1835)
      - Clippings, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 1836)
      - Clippings, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 1837)
      - Clippings, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 1838-1839)
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 1840-1841)
      - Clippings, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 1842-1843)
      - Clippings, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 1844-1846)
      - Clippings, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 1847)
      - Clippings, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 1848)
      - Clippings, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 1849)
      - Clippings, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 1850)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 1851)
    - Greek
      - Clippings, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 1852)
    - Hebrew
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 1853)
    - Hungarian
      - Clippings, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 1854)
      - Clippings, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1855)
    - Italian
      - Clippings, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 1856)
      - Clippings, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 1857)
      - Clippings, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 1858)
      - Clippings, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 1859)
        Includes an article from 1967 photocopied on the same page
      - Clippings, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 1860-1861)
      - Clippings, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 1862)
      - Clippings, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 1863)
      - Clippings, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 1864)
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 1865)
      - Clippings, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 1866)
      - Clippings, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 1867)
      - Clippings, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 1868)
      - Clippings, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 1869)
      - Clippings, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 1870)
      - Clippings, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 1871)
      - Clippings, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 1872)
      - Clippings, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 1873)
      - Clippings, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 1874)
      - Clippings, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 1875)
      - Clippings, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 1876)
      - Clippings, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 1877)
      - Clippings, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 1878)
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 1879)
      - Clippings, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1880)
      - Clippings, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 1881)
      - Clippings, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 1882)
      - Clippings, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 1883)
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 1884)
      - Clippings, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 1885)
      - Clippings, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 1886)
      - Clippings, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 1887)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 87, Folder 1888)
    - Lithuanian
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 1889)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 87, Folder 1890)
    - Polish
      - Clippings, 1933 (Box 88, Folder 1891)
      - Clippings, 1939 (Box 88, Folder 1892)
        Includes French translations
      - Clippings, 1940 (Box 88, Folder 1893)
      - Clippings, 1941 (Box 88, Folder 1894)
      - Clippings, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 1895)
      - Clippings, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 1896)
      - Clippings, 1957 (Box 88, Folder 1897)
      - Clippings, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 1898)
      - Clippings, 1959 (Box 88, Folder 1899)
      - Clippings, 1963 (Box 89, Folder 1900)
      - Clippings, 1965 (Box 89, Folder 1901)
      - Clippings, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 1902)
      - Clippings, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 1903)
      - Clippings, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1904)
        Includes WG's articles
      - Clippings, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 1905-1906)
      - Clippings, 1970 (Box 90, Folder 1907-1908)
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 1909)
      - Clippings, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1910)
      - Clippings, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1911-1913)
      - Clippings, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 1914-1921)
      - Clippings, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 1922-1928)
      - Clippings, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 1929-1936)
        Includes French translations and notes
      - Clippings, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 1937-1944)
      - Clippings, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 1945-1950)
      - Clippings, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 1951-1955)
        Includes note in French
      - Clippings, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 1956-1960)
      - Clippings, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 1961-1964)
      - Clippings, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 1965-1969)
      - Clippings, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 1970)
      - Clippings, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 1971)
        Includes a note in French
      - Clippings, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 1972)
      - Clippings, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 1973-1974)
        Includes French notes and translations
      - Clippings, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 1975-1978)
        Includes French translations and a fragment of a book
      - Clippings, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 1979-1981)
      - Clippings, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 1982)
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 1983)
      - Clippings, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 1984)
      - Clippings, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 1985)
        Includes a French translation
      - Clippings, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 1986)
      - Clippings, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 1987-1988)
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1989)
        Includes a note in English
      - Clippings, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 1990-1992)
      - Clippings, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 1993)
        Includes an English translation
      - Clippings, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 1994)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 1995-1997)
    - Portuguese
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 105, Folder 1998)
      - Clippings, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 1999)
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 2000)
    - Rumanian
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 2001)
      - Clippings, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 2002)
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 2003)
    - Russian
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 2004)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 2005)
    - Serbian
      - Clippings, 1970 (Box 105, Folder 2006)
      - Clippings, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 2007)
      - Clippings, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 2008)
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 2009)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 2010)
    - Spanish
      - Clippings, 1939 (Box 106, Folder 2011)
      - Clippings, 1944 (Box 106, Folder 2012)
      - Clippings, 1947 (Box 106, Folder 2013)
      - Clippings, 1949 (Box 106, Folder 2014)
      - Clippings, 1956 (Box 106, Folder 2015)
      - Clippings, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 2016)
      - Clippings, 1961 (Box 106, Folder 2017)
      - Clippings, 1962 (Box 106, Folder 2018)
      - Clippings, 1963 (Box 106, Folder 2019)
      - Clippings, 1964 (Box 106, Folder 2020)
        Includes a French article photocopied together with the Spanish
      - Clippings, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 2021)
      - Clippings, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 2022)
      - Clippings, 1967 (Box 107, Folder 2023)
        Includes WG's notes
      - Clippings, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 2024)
      - Clippings, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 2025)
      - Clippings, 1970 (Box 107, Folder 2026)
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 2027)
      - Clippings, 1972 (Box 107, Folder 2028)
      - Clippings, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 2029)
      - Clippings, 1974 (Box 107, Folder 2030)
        Contains an issue of La Opinión Cultural
      - Clippings, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 2031)
      - Clippings, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 2032)
      - Clippings, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 2033)
      - Clippings, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 2034)
      - Clippings, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 2035)
      - Clippings, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 2036)
      - Clippings, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 2037)
      - Clippings, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 2038)
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 2039)
      - Clippings, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 2040)
      - Clippings, 1993 (Box 108, Folder 2041)
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 2042)
      - Clippings, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 2043)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 2044)
    - Swedish
      - Clippings, 1959 (Box 109, Folder 2045)
      - Clippings, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 2046)
      - Clippings, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 2047)
      - Clippings, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 2048)
      - Clippings, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 2049)
        Includes Polish translations
      - Clippings, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 2050)
      - Clippings, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 2051)
      - Clippings, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 2052)
      - Clippings, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 2053)
      - Clippings, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 2054)
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 2055)
      - Clippings, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 2056)
      - Clippings, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 2057)
      - Clippings, 1993 (Box 109, Folder 2058)
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 109, Folder 2059)
      - Clippings, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 2060)
      - Clippings, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 2061)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 2062)
    - Yiddish
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 2063)
- Posters, 1963-97; Series XII; 97
  Series XII is organized into six subseries: Festivals, Exhibitions, Theater Adaptations, Plays, Movie Posters, and Publications
  - FESTIVALS
    - XVI Festiwal Polskich Sztuk Wspólczesnych, Wroclaw, 1975 May 24-31
      - Poster, 1975 (Box bsd, folder 2064)
        Size: 94.5 x 67.5 cm.
      - Program, 1975 (Box bsd, folder 2065)
    - Espace Acteur "Un mois de la Pologne à Paris", [1990] (Box bsd, folder 2066)
      Size: 54 x 41 cm.
    - I Miedzynarodowy Festival Gombrowiczowski Radom 1993, design by Wiktor Sadowski (2 copies) (Box bsd, folder 2067)
      Size: 94.5 x 65 cm.
    - II, Miedzynarodowy Festiwal
    - Gombrowiczowski Radom 1995
      - Program, 1995 (Box bsd, folder 2068)
        Size: 100.5 x 71 cm.
      - Program corrected, 1995 (Box bsd, folder 2069)
        Size: 98 x 71 cm.
      - Festival poster, design by Wiktor Sadowski (2 copies), 1995 (Box bsd, folder 2070)
        Size 98 x 69 cm.
    - III Miedzynarodowy Festiwal Gombrowiczowski Radom 1997
      - Program, [1997] (Box bsd, folder 2071)
        Size: 101 x 71 cm.
      - Festiwal poster, design by Wieslaw Walkuski (2 copies), 1997 (Box bsd, folder 2072)
        Size: 99 x 68.5 cm.
      - Information about the sponsors and media coverage (2 copies), 1997 (Box bsd, folder 2073)
        Size: 60.5 x 43 cm.
      - [Teatr w Radomiu], Tancerz Mecenasa Krajkowskiego [Krzysztof Warlikowski], [1997] (Box bsd, folder 2074)
        Size: 102 x 36 cm.
  - EXHIBITIONS
    - Teatr Nowy w Warszawie, "Gombrowicz z przodu i z tylu" [exhibition of posters], 1984 (Box bsd, folder 2075)
      Size: 100 x 70.5 cm.
    - Teatr Nowy w Warszawie, "Gombrowicz z przodu i z tylu", design by Waldemar Swierzy, n.d. (Box bsd, folder 2076)
      Size: 98 x 69 cm.
    - Stichting Literaire Activiteiten Amsterdam, 1986 Sep 21 (Box bsd, folder 2077)
      Size: 46 x 33 cm.
    - Stichting Literaire Activiteiten Amsterdam (2 copies), 1986 Sep 21 (Box bsd, folder 2078)
      Size: 64 x 31 cm.
    - Université de Montreal, meeting with RG 1990 Mar 14 (2 copies) (Box bsd, folder 2079)
      Size: 44 x 29 cm.
    - "Witold Gombrowicz", Centre Georges Pompidou, Paris, 1991 Mar 27- Jun 10, design by Jan Lenica (2 copies) (Box bsd, folder 2080)
      Size 71 x 51 cm.
    - "Witold Gombrowicz", Villa Alexandrine, Vence, 1992 Feb 7- Mar 12
      - Poster, 1992 (Box bsd, folder 2081)
        Size: 80.5 x 60 cm.
      - Poster, design by Jan Lenica (2 copies), 1992 (Box bsd, folder 2082)
        Size: 61 x 41 cm.
    - Université de Toulouse le Mirail, "Gombrowicz passionné de Gombrowicz", 1993 May 11-14 (Box bsd, folder 2083)
    - Mairie de Paris and Bibliothèque de Buffon, "Gombrowicz et son double", exposition 1996 Nov 12-30 (3 copies) (Box bsd, folder 2084)
    - "Gombrowicz na zamku" (Poznan), 1996 Mar 19-Apr 10 (Box bsd, folder 2085)
      Size: 59 x 46 cm.
    - "Witold Gombrowicz verfilmd" (Hague, Netherlands), program, n.y. Mar-Apr (Box bsd, folder 2086)
      Size: 62.5 x 45 cm.
    - Association des Amis de Witold Gombrowicz, "Hommage à Witold Gombrowicz", program (Box bsd, folder 2087)
    - Centro Cultural "La Hendija", "Gombrowicz o La Seducción" (Box bsd, folder 2088)
      Size: 46.5 x 37 cm.
  - THEATER ADAPTATIONS
    - Biesiada u hrabiny Kotlubaj
      - Troupe de T.M.B. [Tomasz Bialkowski], 1995 Jun 23, 30 (Box bsd, folder 2089)
        Size: 41 x 61 cm.
      - Scena Prezentacje, Romuald Szejd, design by Andrzej Krynicki (Box bsd, folder 2090)
        Joint with Zbrodnia z premedytacja
        Size: 64 x 59 cm.
    - Dziewictwo
      - Teatr Nowy w Poznaniu, [Izabela Cywinska], n.d. (Box bsd, folder 2091)
        Size: 62 x 31 cm.
    - Ferdydurke
      - Teatr Nowy w Poznaniu [Waldemar Smigasiewicz], 1991 Jan 11 (Box bsd, folder 2092)
        Size: 88 x 63 cm.
      - Teatr Wspólczesny we Wroclawiu [Jacek Bunsch], 1997 Jun (Box bsd, folder 2093)
        Size: 122 x 87 cm.
    - Kosmos
      - Teatr w Radomiu, [Waldemar Smigasiewicz] (2 copies), n.d. (Box bsd, folder 2094)
        Size: 69 x 43 cm.
    - Opetani
      - Teatr Polski we Wroclawiu, [Tadeusz Minc], 1980 May (Box bsd, folder 2095)
        Size: 86 x 61 cm.
    - Pornografia
      - Teatr Nowy w Lodzi [Wojciech Szulczynski], 1988 Mar 25 (Box bsd, folder 2096)
        Size: 71 x 50.5 cm.
    - Tancerz mecenasa Kraykowskiego
      - Compagnie de Réverbère, [Jörg Schnass], n.d. (Box bsd, folder 2097)
        Size: 43 x 30.5 cm.
    - Trans-Atlantyk
      - Teatr im. Stefana Jaracza w Lodzi [Mikolaj Grabowski], 1981 May 16 (Box bsd, folder 2098)
        Size: 69.5 x 50.5 cm.
      - Teatr Polski we Wroclawiu, [Eugeniusz Korin], 1982 Mar (Box bsd, folder 2099)
        Size: 101 x 68.5 cm.
      - Teatr Polski we Wroclawiu, 1982 (Box bsd, folder 2100)
        Size: 97 x 68 cm.
      - Teatr Slaski im. Stanislawa Wyspianskiego w Katowicach, [Mikolaj Grabowski], 1993 May (Box bsd, folder 2101)
        Size: 69 x 50.5 cm.
    - Other Adaptations
      - Ja, Gombrowicz, Teatr Nowy w Lodzi Wojciech Szulczynski, 1988 Mar 25 (Box bsd, folder 2102)
        Size: 71 x 51 cm.
      - Memoires du temps de l'immaturité, Cie Ariadne, 1990 Nov 20-24 (Box bsd, folder 2103)
      - Czaber z Gombra, Teatr Nowy w Warszawie [Adam Hanuszkiewicz], [1992] (Box bsd, folder 2104)
        Size:95 x 68 cm.
      - La Lycéenne et Gombrowicz, Centre d'Animation du Forum des Halles [Catherine Espinasse] (Box bsd, folder 2105)
        Size:58 x 39 cm.
      - La Lycéenne et Gombrowicz, Centre d'Animation du Forum des Halles [Catherine Espinasse] (Box bsd, folder 2105a)
        Size: 44 x 31.5 cm.
  - PLAYS
    - Historia
      - Teatr Polski we Wroclawiu, [Jacek Bunsch], 1985 Feb (Box bsd, folder 2106)
        Size: 69 x 99 cm.
      - Theatergruppe 80 (Vien), 1985 Jan (Box bsd, folder 2107)
        Size: 85 x 60 cm.